export const questions = [
    {
        "planet": [
            {
                "question": "In which year INSERT_NAME was born?",
                "requiredAnotherApiShot": "false",
                "requiredAnswer": "birth_year",
                "possibleNAOrUnknownAnswers": ""
            },
            {
                "question": "What height is INSERT_NAME?",
                "requiredAnotherApiShot": "false",
                "requiredAnswer": "height",
                "possibleNAOrUnknownAnswers": ""
            },
            {
                "question": "What planet is INSERT_NAME from?",
                "requiredAnotherApiShot": "true",
                "requiredAnswer": "homeworld",
                "possibleNAOrUnknownAnswers": ""
            },
            {
                "question": "How much does INSERT_NAME weigh?",
                "requiredAnotherApiShot": "false",
                "requiredAnswer": "mass",
                "possibleNAOrUnknownAnswers": ""
            },
            {
                "question": "What color are INSERT_NAME's hair?",
                "requiredAnotherApiShot": "false",
                "requiredAnswer": "hair_color",
                "possibleNAOrUnknownAnswers": ""
            },
            {
                "question": "What color are INSERT_NAME's eyes?",
                "requiredAnotherApiShot": "false",
                "requiredAnswer": "eye_color",
                "possibleNAOrUnknownAnswers": ""
            }
        ],
        "planets": [
            {
                "question": "What is the rotation period of INSERT_NAME?",
                "requiredAnotherApiShot": "false",
                "requiredAnswer": "rotation_period",
                "possibleNAOrUnknownAnswers": ""
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the orbital period of INSERT_NAME?",
                "requiredAnotherApiShot": "false",
                "requiredAnswer": "orbital_period",
                "possibleNAOrUnknownAnswers": ""
            },
            {
                "question": "What diameter is INSERT_NAME?",
                "requiredAnotherApiShot": "false",
                "requiredAnswer": "diameter",
                "possibleNAOrUnknownAnswers": ""
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the climate like at INSERT_NAME?",
                "requiredAnotherApiShot": "false",
                "requiredAnswer": "climate",
                "possibleNAOrUnknownAnswers": ""
            },
            {
                "question": "How much gravity is on INSERT_NAME?",
                "requiredAnotherApiShot": "false",
                "requiredAnswer": "gravity",
                "possibleNAOrUnknownAnswers": ""
            },
            {
                "question": "What kind of terrain prevails on INSERT_NAME?",
                "requiredAnotherApiShot": "false",
                "requiredAnswer": "terrain",
                "possibleNAOrUnknownAnswers": ""
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the population on INSERT_NAME?",
                "requiredAnotherApiShot": "false",
                "requiredAnswer": "population",
                "possibleNAOrUnknownAnswers": ""
            }
        ]
    }
]